(crowd cheering)
(upbeat lively music)
♪ Born down in a dead man's town ♪
♪ The first kick I took
was when I hit the ground ♪
♪ You end up like a dog
that's been beat too much ♪
♪ Till you spend half your
life just to cover it up now ♪
♪ Born in the U.S.A. ♪
♪ I was born in the U.S.A. ♪
♪ Born in the U.S.A., now ♪
♪ Got in a little hometown jam ♪
♪ So they put a rifle in my hand ♪
♪ Sent me off to a foreign land ♪
♪ To go and kill the yellow man ♪
♪ Born in the U.S.A. ♪
♪ I was born in the U.S.A. ♪
♪ Come back home to the refinery ♪
♪ Hiring man says, Son,
if it was up to me ♪
♪ Went down to see my V.A. man ♪
♪ He said, Son, don't you understand now ♪
(upbeat lively music continues)
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, come on ♪
♪ Come on, now ♪
♪ I had a brother at Khe Sahn ♪
♪ Fighting off them Viet Cong ♪
♪ They're still there, he's all gone ♪
(upbeat lively music continues)
♪ He had a woman he loved in Saigon ♪
♪ I got a picture of him in her arms now ♪
♪ Down in the shadow of the penitentiary ♪
♪ Out by the gas fires of the refinery ♪
♪ I'm 10 years burning down the road ♪
♪ Nowhere to run, ain't
got nowhere to go ♪
♪ Born in the U.S.A. ♪
♪ I was born in the U.S.A., now ♪
♪ I'm a long gone daddy
in the U.S.A., now ♪
♪ Born in the U.S.A. ♪
♪ I'm a cool, rockin'
daddy in the U.S.A., now ♪
(upbeat lively music continues)
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Come on, now ♪
♪ Oh no, no ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Whoa, no, no, no ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
(Bruce vocalizing)
(upbeat lively music continues)
♪ Yeah, I was ♪
(crowd cheering and clapping)
(upbeat lively music continues)